<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TechSphere</string>
    <string name="laptopTxt">ASUS VivoBook 15, the epitome of style, performance, and versatility in a sleek package. Designed to meet the needs of modern-day users,
        this laptop seamlessly blends cutting-edge technology with a stunning design,
        making it the perfect companion for work, entertainment, and everything in between.
        At the heart of the ASUS VivoBook 15 lies a powerful Intel Core processor,
        delivering lightning-fast performance and seamless multitasking capabilities with a
        vibrant 15.6-inch Full HD display.\n\n
        Order now and immerse yourself in the boundless possibilities of the digital world.</string>

    <string name="consoleTxt">Prepare to embark on an unparalleled gaming journey with the highly anticipated PS-5 Digital.
        Assembled with cutting-edge technology and designed to cater to the modern gamer,
        this console transcends boundaries, delivering a seamless and immersive gaming encounter
        like never before. The PS-5 Digital comes paired with the innovative DualSense controller,
        redefining the way you interact with your games. With haptic feedback and adaptive triggers,
        every sensation is magnified, offering a heightened level of immersion.\n\n
        Order now and immerse yourself in the boundless possibilities of the digital world.</string>

    <string name="phoneTxt"> Elevating the standards of excellence yet again, the IPhone 14
        pushes the boundaries of what\'s possible, delivering a seamless fusion of power,
        performance, and elegance. Powered by the latest A-series chip, the iPhone 14 offers unparalleled
        performance that effortlessly handles everything you throw at it.
        From multitasking with ease to running graphics-intensive games flawlessly,
        this device ensures a smooth and responsive user experience at every turn.\n\n
        Order yours today and experience innovation like never before.</string>

    <string name="visionTxt">Apple\'s Vision Pro is a virtual reality headset that displays high-resolution
        graphics and lets users control a desktop interface using their eyes and hand gestures.
        It has a curved laminated glass display, aluminum frame, flexible cushion, and adjustable headband.
        The frame contains five sensors, six microphones, and 12 cameras.
        The Vision Pro is controlled by voice, eyes, and hands, and has no controllers.
        The Vision Pro has an external battery that supports up to 2 hours of general
        use and up to 2.5 hours of video playback. \n\n
        Explore the endless possibilities of Augmented Reality with Apple Vision Pro today!</string>

    <string name="audioTxt">AirPods Pro – the next evolution in wireless audio technology.\n\n
        Designed for the modern lifestyle, AirPods Pro offer a perfect blend of style, comfort, and performance.
        The iconic AirPods design has been refined to fit even more comfortably in your ears,
        providing a secure and snug fit for all-day wear. Equipped with custom-designed drivers,
        these earbuds deliver rich, immersive sound with deep bass and crisp highs.
        Whether you\'re listening to your favorite music, taking calls, or watching movies,
        AirPods 3 ensure an exceptional audio experience every time.\n\n
    Upgrade to AirPods Pro and elevate your listening experience to new heights.</string>
</resources>